Guide to the Liberty Hyde Bailey papers, 1845-2004
Bailey, Liberty Hyde papers, 1845-2004
- Series VI. Hortorium and Plant Collecting, 1887 - 1959
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Lundell, C.C., 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Lyle - Lynch, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: MacDaniel - Marks, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Marsakese - Massey, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Matlock - May, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: McAtee - McWilliams, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Meigs - Metcalf, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Michel - Miller, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Minnesota - Moe, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Moldenke, H.N., 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Monroe - Montgomery, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Monticelli - Moore, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Morales Valcarcel - Morton, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Moscoso - Mowry, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Mullen - Myers, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Nanking - Newman, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: New York Botanical Garden: 09/39 - 10/40, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: New York Botanical Garden: 01/39 - 08/39, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: New York State Cancer Committee - Nimon, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Noble - North Carolina, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Nuttall - Oxford University Press, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Paasche - Parrott, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Pearce - Penick, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Pennell, F.W., 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Perley - Peynado, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Philipines - Pittier, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Plant Quarantine - Plymale, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Poe - Potter, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Pratt - Pridham, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Puerto Rico - Purer, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Questel, A., 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Quick - Quisumbing, 1939 - 1940 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ramsbottom - Ramsey's, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rappleye - Reeves, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rehder, Alfred, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rehder, Alfred, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Reisner - Rhodora, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rijksherbarium - Rimoldi, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rio de Janeiro - Robinson, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rockwell - Roewekamp, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rogalsky - Rollins, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rose - Rossberg, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Routon -Royal, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Runyon - Ryerson, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Saint John - Saunders, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Scanlon - Scarborough, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Schader - Schramm, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Schultes, R.E., 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Schwarten - Schweinfurth, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Scott - Seibert, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Seifriz, W., 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Selden - Seymour, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Sharp - Shaw, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Sherwood - Sloughter, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Smith - Smithsonian, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Sneguiried - Soule, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Spencer - Sprague, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Stacey - State, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Stearn - Stevens, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Stimson - Styer, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Superintendant - Sylvain, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Tanimura - Taylor, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Teas - Texas, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Tharp - Thompson, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Tillinghast - Towson, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Tphilisi - True, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Tukey - Tuskegee, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ulich - Uno, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Van Beek - Van Melle, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Van Rensselaer - Vaughan, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Verdoorn, F., 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Verhalen - Voth, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wahl, H.A., 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Waldo - Walton, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ware - Waugh, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wayside Gardens Co., 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Weatherby - Webster, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Weld - Wells, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: West, Erdman, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Westbury - Weymouth, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wharton - Whitlow, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wigley -Wilson, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wirth -Wilson, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wolfe - Woods, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Woodson, R.E., 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Woytkowski - Wyman, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Yale - Yust, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Z, 1939 - 1940 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Aaronson - Agricultural, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Allard, H.A., 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Allen, P.H., 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Allen, R. - Alling, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: American B. - Ames, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Anderson E. - Armstrong, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Arnold, B.G. - Arnold Arboretum, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Atkins - Auchter, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Babcock - Baker, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Balch - Bancroft, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Barbour - Barry, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bartlett - Barton, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Beadle - Begonian, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bell - Bessey, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bibbins - Blakeslee, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bomhard - Boonstra, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bornsewitz - Bowne, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bradfield - Braunton, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Breed - Bristol, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Brown, H.O. - Brown, H.O., 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Brooklyn - Brown, C.A., 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bucher - Burkart, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Burnette - Burret, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Buswell, W.M., 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Butterworth - Buzby, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cabrera - Calvo, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Campbell - Canizares, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Carabia - Carter, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Catholic University -Cayuga, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Caeseres - Castle, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Chardon - Chase, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cherry - Cintron, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Clapp - Clausen, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Clokey, I - C.M. & I College, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cockerell - Coker, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Coleman - Columbia University, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Compton - Conzatti, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cook - Coon, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Core, E.L., 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cornell - Cornman, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cory, V.L., 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cosline - Cowles, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cranbrook Institute of Science, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Creasy - Cross, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cuellar - Cumby, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cutak, Ladislaus, 1941 - 1943 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Dahlberg, K, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Dahlgren, B.E., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Dakin - Darrow, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Davidson, J. - Davis, E.B., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Davis, L.I., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Davis, R.J. - Dayton, W.A., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Deam - Degener, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Delaware - Denmark, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Descole - Detjen, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Dichondra - Dietx, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Doris - Dow, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Dreer - Drysdale, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Dudley - Duman, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Duncan - Dutilly, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Eames - Eastwood, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Edgerton - Egler, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Eichling, Mrs. C.W. - Eichling, C.W., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ellis - Engard, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Epling, Carl, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ericson - Eustace, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Evans - Eyerdam, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Fairchild - Fall, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Farrar - Fassett, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Federal - F"&"F, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Field - Fitzgerald, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Fleming - Flory, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Fogg, John M., Jr., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Fosberg - Fox, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Franco - Furtado, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Gage - George, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Gibson - Glazener, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Gleason, H.A., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Gleason - Goldman, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Goodman - Goodson, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Goodspeed, T.H., 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Gourd - Gourley, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Graham - Graves, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Gray & Cole - Gray Herbarium, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Greenman - Gregory, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Griffing - Grover, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Guanajuato - Guzman, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Haines - Hancin, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hanes, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hannah - J.M. Harper, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: R.M. Harper, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Harrington - Hazeltine, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Head - Herrick, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hershey - Hill, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hobson - Hodson, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hogansville - Horsey, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Horticultural - Howland, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hubricht - Hume, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hunziker - Hyland, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Income - Jessep, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Jiminez, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Johnston - Joyner, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Junge - Keyes, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Killip, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: King - Knudson, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Kohankie - Ladd, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Lagomarsino - LaPlata, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Larrabee - Lawrence, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Le Cointe - Lever, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Lewis - Lillo, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Lindsay - Loucks, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Love - Lynch, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Macbride - Mann, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Manning - Maruzen, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Mason - Massey, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Mauldin - Mayer, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: McCallan - McVaugh, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Mendenhall - Meyer, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Miami - Mitchell, 1941 - 1943 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Moldenke, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Moles - Moore, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Moreland - Morton, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Moscoso - Muller, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Munz - Myers, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Narcotics - Newman, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: New York, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Nik-Nar - Olmo, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Orange - Parish, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Park - Paul, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Pearce - Pellett, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Penfound - Perky, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Perret - Petry, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Philpott - Pohl, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Pollard - Pride, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Princeton - Quisumbung, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ralston - Reasoner, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Record - Reisner, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Reiter - Richards, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ricker - Roewekamp, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rogalsky - Rosendahl, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ross - Ryerson, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Sage - Savercool, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Schaeffer - Scott, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Scribner - Seymour, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Sharp - Shutt, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Sicard - Smiley, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Smith - Smithsonian, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Snyder - Stearn, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Stechert - Sylvain, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Tanaka - Texas, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Tharp - Towsley, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Trelease - Tuskegee, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Ulich - Von Melle, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Van Rensselaer - Von Lilienthal, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wahl - Ware, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Washington - Weatherby, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Webber - Weymarn, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wharton - Willcox, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Williams - Wister, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Wodehouse - Wolfe, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Woodson, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Worcestershire - Zwickey, 1941 - 1943 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Abbot - Alter, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Altman - Bancroft, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bancroft - Beers, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Bell - Boerner, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Borsch - British, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Brooklyn - Butts, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cabot - Cass, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Catchpole - City, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Clausen - Conzatti, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cook - Cowgill, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Cranbrook - Cutak, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Dahlgren - Degener, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Delacroix - Dreer, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: du Bois - Eisenhart, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Elliot - Ewing, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Fairchild - Ferrall, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Fielder - Fox, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Frakes - Gazin, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Geiser - Gourley, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Graham - Greggs, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Griffith - Guthrie, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hagerty - Hancin, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hanes, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hannah - Harper, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Harris - Head, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Heath, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hedrick - Hoehne, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hoover - Howland, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Hume - Hyland, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Illinois - Johnston, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Jones - Keyes, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Killip - Ladner, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: LaMont - Lawrence, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Learbury - Leydendecker, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Library - Lynch, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: MacCaughey - Martinez, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Mason - Massey, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Matthews - May, 1944 - 1945 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: McClelland - McVaugh, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Meira - Mitchell, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Mock - Moore, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Moran - Munz, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Nasarevich - Ownbey, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Paddock - Pennell, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Perkins - Powell, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Pratt - Quibel, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rancho - Rhodora, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rice - Roewekamp, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Rogalsky - Rynalski, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Hortorium Correspondence: Sage - Senn, 1944 - 1945 (Box 10, Folder 12)